Q.What about the black outfit? A.I wore black because I am Hess.
Q. What about the black outfit? A.I wore black clothes suddenly, too.
Q. What is your black outfit? A.I have black hair because I am a black hess.
Q. What about the black outfit? A.I have been wearing it for a while.
Q. What about the black outfit? A. It's been around for a while.
To your hearts for more than the most worldwide.
In addition, we are Juice-Juice, so please give us your best regards.
It was Juice-Juice.
Please also the number 2.
Number 2 is fine.
I would like to use number 4.
Se-no.
Yes, sir.
Roth will start, so turn around with Aki-chan.
I'm already sadder than anyone else.
I'm going to make your wishes come true.
Dreams, thoughts...
Dreams are still dreams, I'll meet you through the window and we'll have a good time
Why, I was even afraid to let you jump on board
Aiming for the stars, Starlin' Star Rinse
Drawing a cross section of the future
NEXT COUNTRY IS
ON THE WAVES
Goo, yay, yay, yay!
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Please do.
Please take care of them.
Go this way.Okay, go this way.
What is this?
Onigiri.
It's a crispy rice ball.
Oh, wow.
So there are dogs and stuff.
Oh, a dog.
Of course, I'll keep as many as I like.
I will feed them onigiri.
Really.
Oh, you mean that?
It's only black and white.
These are so delicious. Every one.
Matcha.
So good.
Hot.
Hero.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Icesotube!
I fucking tube?
No, no, no.
I'm not very skilled.
Don't you always look at my instagram and like it?
I'm still embarrassed.
She's cute. She's so cute.
What do you think?
What's going on?What's going on?
Please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Now it might take some time.
Yay.
Thank you.
Good luck with the show.
I'll watch it when I can.
Thank you.
Please use this place for sure.
I cut a lot.
I cut more than 20 cm off my face.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
Oh no.
I'm off.
Let me say hello.
Okay.
Four, five, six.
Lock on to your heart, Mr. No Way!
We are the biggest fatties in the world.
Nice to meet you.
Please take care of us.
Let's have fun.
Please enjoy yourself.
We will do our best.
Please do.
I usually put on whitening cream.I usually put on whitening cream.
But today was a black festival, so I came as I was.
I usually apply it.
I have a toning cream that I use when I enter the festival,
You don't apply it?
No, I don't.
Today, I came as I am,
Today, on the contrary, it was good to paint it black.
That's right. Like when you did Hiyopoyo.
You should have painted it.
It comes out every year.
That's right.
Everyone.
Aki-chan also had her make-up done as Bigelow.
Julia was surprisingly great, too, since she was in gal makeup.
Julia was good, too.
Julia brought her own black one. The black one.
I wanted to shade everything.
That's my original Indonesian tan color.
Everyone loves it.
I got so burnt. I got so black.
I was eating a full tank of food, right? I'm sure.
About a ton.
Delicious.
Oh, it's so close.
than
Than
more than more than more than
yes and no
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Have a good time.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, stickers are stickers are stickers are stickers
There it is.
Yes, stickers.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
It's in the bag.
Thank you very much.
I'm off.
Thank you for watching.
I'll do my best!
Thanks for your hard work!
I sweated a lot! It was fun!
Thanks a lot!
You worked up a sweat!
My sweat turned black!
I was sweating so much.
It was amazing!
It was so much fun!
It's great! Everyone had a great time!
Even the non-promoters were awesome!
You guys had a great time!
There were even some PR people in the back!
Yes! So, thank you very much for the black hair soup!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work! Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!!!
So, thank you for the black hair soup!
Thank you very much!
It's been a while since we were on the show.
How was it?
It was super exciting! It was like a party!
It was amazing!
It was so hot and warm and exciting!
It was like Hino-chan went to the waterfall dormitory!
It was so hot!
I was really surprised!
You were probably hotter than anyone else in the venue!
Really! But you know what, it was super fun!
It was a lot of fun!
Great! I love this kind of technology!
Those who don't know about the special editions?
Even those who wear other people's goods
They were so excited and sold a lot of stuff!
It was so much fun!
Great summer memories!
I feel like I rocked it!
Yes! I feel like we did!
It was so much fun!
Thank you so much!
Next stop is the tour!
I'll do my best for the floor finals!
I don't know the scenery, here, let's go to anywhere.
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the streets are changing colors After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint shards of the future.
It leads me to the future.
Subtitle: Kiminomiya
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Time will soon remind me
So that I can smile even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye, Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets sparkle
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Thank you for watching!